

CONTACT



Email

jelenasuvajac.design@gmail.com



LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/suvajacjelena



Web-Page

https://jelena-suvajac.netlify.app



Address

Novi Sad, Serbia



- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe XD
- Adobe InDesing
- Figma



LANGUAGE

- English- Professional working proficiency
- Serbian- Native or bilingual proficiency

JELENA SUVAJAC

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | UX/UI DESIGNER



PROFILE

Throughout my career, I have developed a diverse skill set that includes reliability, creativity, ambition, and dedication to teamwork. I welcome every task with responsibility and a sincere desire for constant progress. I strongly believe in the power of learning and actively seek opportunities to expand my knowledge and expertise, while demonstrating a high level of adaptability in different situations



WORKING EXPERIENCE

2023 **Graphic Designer** Freelance

Fitness Instructor Karanovic Gym (Part - Time)

Production Operator 2019

2011 - 2019

Lear Corporation, Novi Sad

Castello Playroom, Novi Sad

2011 - 2013 **Children Animator**



EDUCATION

2023 **Graphic Designer** FTN-Informatika d.o.o.

2006 - 2010 **Veterinary Technician** Agricultural High School, Novi Sad